<cline-context>
    <rules>
        <rule>
            Never start an import with `from src.`. src is not a module. Also never
            use relative imports beyond a single `.` for same package.  We use
            a setup.py file to implement this standard.  We also indicate in a vscode
            settings file to open all terminals in a venv.
        </rule>
        <rule>
            You're an experienced senior python engineer. You know how to set up
            a python project correctly using best practices. You never use hacks like setting
            environment variables to get scripts to run. You're an expert at how python works
            under the hood and how python scripts are supposed to be run. Moreover, if you see
            a project is not running as you expect, rather than hacking your way toward a solution,
            you criticize the project and fix it to use a correct directory and file structure
            in accordance with best practices for modern python development.
        </rule>
        <rule>Do not use `ls -R`, there are too many files and it will print too much.</rule>
        <rule>Use `pyright src` to check compiler errors and `pytest` to run unit tests after every
            major
            change.
            Also run `pyright test` for the test code. Use strong typing aggressively. Major
            service functions that are expected to be called by other files should define a request
            and response object data structure.</rule>
        <rule> DO NOT use try-except and do not write None-checks. Strong-type everything and use
            Optional[Foo] if it really is an expected case that the Foo can be present or absent.
            Use assertions to coerce to Foo or throw if Foo is not optional according to "business
            logic". A common example of this is XML parsing errors from LLM responses. The issue is
            almost never that the LLM returned a bad response but that the prompt is misaligned with
            the code. In such cases, we need to fail fast (as always) and fix the prompt. <rule>Don't
            let files exceed 100 lines.
                Break them into modules when they reach this point.</rule>
        <rule>Update the
            `reference` section
                of this XML doc with `note`s.</rule>
        </rule>
        <rule>Keep source code files under 100 lines so they are AI assistant-friendly.  When you think a file
            needs to grow larger, split it and make it more modular. 
        </rule>
        <rule>Inline comments are almost always bad and a code smell.  Good code should
            explain itself.
        </rule>
        <rule>No try-excepts.  Fail fast everywhere possible.</rule>
        <rule>Primary git branch is `master`.</rule>
    </rules>

    <long-term-memory>
        <note>
            I'm building a simple API and UI to automate a workflow
            for doing an image face-swap using an existing API.  
        </note>
    </long-term-memory>

    <current-task>
      Make sure the fastAPI API works by running it locally and 
      sending it a test request. 
    </current-task>
    <next-task>
        src/scripts/faceswap_experiment now has a "successful experiment"
        in that the Faceswap API client is now working in the sense that
        it can send a successful request to the faceswap API to swap faces
        on two images given by their public URLs.  

        face_swap.app runs an API that I think works.  Send it a test
        request to make sure. 

        Write a simplest-possible frontend that exhibits this, allowing the
        user to upload two photos, a "source face" and a "target image" into
        which the face will be transplanted.  

        It is likely that I'll need to give you access to my public S3 bucket
        because public image URLs need to be sent to the API.  Assume any
        API keys and AWS necessities are in .env and I will put them in
        for you. 
    </next-task>
</cline-context>